（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
- 什么是动态填充？
- What is dynamic padding?
在 “一起批量输入” 视频中，
In the "Batching Inputs together" video,
我们已经看到能够对输入进行分组
we have seen that to be able to group inputs
同一批不同长度的，
of different lengths in the same batch,
我们需要向所有短输入添加填充标记
we need to add padding tokens to all the short inputs
直到它们的长度都相同。
until they are all of the same length.
例如，这里最长的句子是第三句，
Here, for instance, the longest sentence is the third one,
我们需要添加五个、两个或七个填充令牌
and we need to add five, two, or seven pad tokens
到其他句子有四个句子
to the other sentences to have four sentences
相同的长度。
of the same lengths.
在处理整个数据集时，
When dealing with a whole dataset,
我们可以应用各种填充策略。
there are various padding strategies we can apply.
最明显的一种是填充所有元素
The most obvious one is to pad all the elements
数据集的相同长度：
of the dataset to the same length:
最长样本的长度。
the length of the longest sample.
这会给我们批次
This will then give us batches
都具有相同的形状
that all have the same shape
由最大序列长度决定。
determined by the maximum sequence length.
缺点是批次由短句组成
The downside is that batches composed from short sentences
会有很多填充令牌
will have a lot of padding tokens
这将在模型中引入更多计算
which will introduce more computations in the model
我们最终不需要。
we ultimately don't need.
为了避免这种情况，另一种策略是填充元素
To avoid this, another strategy is to pad the elements
当我们把它们批在一起时，
when we batch them together,
到批次中最长的句子。
to the longest sentence inside the batch.
这样，由短输入组成的批次会更小
This way, batches composed of short inputs will be smaller
比包含最长句子的批次
than the batch containing the longest sentence
在数据集中。
in the dataset.
这将在 CPU 和 GPU 上产生一些不错的加速。
This will yield some nice speedup on CPU and GPU.
缺点是所有批次
The downside is that all batches
然后会有不同的形状，
will then have different shapes,
这会减慢 TPU 等加速器的训练速度。
which slows down training on accelerators like TPUs.
让我们看看如何在实践中应用这两种策略。
Let's see how to apply both strategies in practice.
我们实际上已经看到了如何应用固定填充
We have actually seen how to apply fixed padding
在数据集概述视频中，
in the Datasets Overview video,
当我们预处理 MRPC 数据集时：
when we preprocessed the MRPC dataset:
加载数据集和分词器后，
after loading the dataset and tokenizer,
我们将标记化应用于所有数据集
we applied the tokenization to all the dataset
带填充和截断
with padding and truncation
制作所有长度为 128 的样本。
to make all samples of length 128.
结果，如果我们传递这个数据集
As a result, if we pass this dataset
到 PyTorch DataLoader，
to a PyTorch DataLoader,
我们得到形状批量大小的批次，这里是 16，乘以 128。
we get batches of shape batch size, here 16, by 128.
要应用动态填充，
To apply dynamic padding,
我们必须将填充推迟到批量准备，
we must defer the padding to the batch preparation,
所以我们从标记化函数中删除了那部分。
so we remove that part from our tokenize function.
我们仍然保留截断部分
We still leave the truncation part
以便大于最大长度的输入
so that inputs that are bigger than the maximum length
被模型接受，通常是 512，
accepted by the model, usually 512,
被截断到那个长度。
get truncated to that length.
然后我们动态地填充我们的样本
Then we pad our samples dynamically
通过使用数据整理器。
by using a data collator.
Transformers 库中的那些类
Those classes in the Transformers library
负责应用所有的最终处理
are responsible for applying all the final processing
在形成批次之前需要，
needed before forming a batch,
这里 DataCollatorWithPadding 将填充样本
here DataCollatorWithPadding will pad the samples
到这批句子中的最大长度。
to the maximum length inside the batch of sentences.
我们将它作为整理函数传递给 PyTorch DataLoader，
We pass it to the PyTorch DataLoader as a collate function,
然后观察生成的批次
then observe that the batches generated
有不同的长度，
have various lengths,
一直低于之前的 128。
all way below the 128 from before.
动态批处理几乎总是更快
Dynamic batching will almost always be faster
在 CPU 和 GPU 上，所以如果可以的话你应该应用它。
on CPUs and GPUs, so you should apply it if you can.
但是，请记住切换回固定填充
Remember to switch back to fixed padding, however,
如果你在 TPU 上运行你的训练脚本
if you run your training script on TPU
或者需要成批的固定形状。
or need batches of fixed shapes.
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)